Guide to the Cherríe Moraga Papers, 1970-1996
Department of Special Collections
- Series XIII. Essays and Reviews
  - Reviews: Giving up the Ghost [Alaniz, Yola. "Front Room's 'Giving up the Ghost' is rare vehicle for Chicana Artists," Seattle Gay News (1987 Apr. 3)] 1987 Apr. 3 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Reviews: Giving up the Ghost [Barnes, Noreen C. "An example of 'Teatropoesia'," San Francisco Bay Area Reporter (1989 Feb. 16)] 1989 Feb. 16 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Reviews: Giving up the Ghost [Cariaga, Caralina. "The poetics of Chisme," Poetry Flash.--No. 195 (1989 June)] 1989 June (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Reviews: Giving up the Ghost [Carroway, Chezia. Review of Ghost. New York Women Against Rape.--Vol. 3, no. 1 (1986 Dec.): 4] 1986 Dec. (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Reviews: Giving up the Ghost [Castillo, Ana. "Giving up the Ghost ," Nuevas Publicaciones (1986)] 1986 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Reviews: Giving up the Ghost [Foster, Sesshu. "Multicultural Poetry: New Books"] n.d. (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Reviews: Giving up the Ghost [Hurwitt, Robert. "A confusion of Ghosts," San Francisco Examiner (1989 Feb. 14)] 1989 Feb. 14 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Reviews: Giving up the Ghost [Lockerbie, Aerie. "Giving up the Ghost," San Francisco Sentinel (1989 Mar. 2)] 1989 Mar. 2 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Reviews: Giving up the Ghost [Sundstrom, Kay. "Deep Rivers of Passion," The Daily Californian (1989 Mar. 3): 10] 1989 Mar. 3 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Reviews: Giving up the Ghost [Trujillo, Carla. "Play treats Latina Lesbianism with sensitivity," El Tecolote (1989 May)] 1989 May (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Reviews: Giving up the Ghost [Turoff, Randy. "Giving up the Ghost" Coming Up (1989 Mar.)] 1989 Mar. (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Reviews: Giving up the Ghost [Warren, Steve. "For Women Mainly: Don't Give up on Ghost," Our Paper (1989 Mar. 8): 14] 1989 Mar. 8 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Reviews: Giving up the Ghost [Weiner, Bernard. "Playsthat fall short of potential," San Francisco Chronicle (1989 Feb. 22) and "Giving up the Ghost," San Francisco Bay Guardian (1989 Mar. 1)] 1989 Feb. -Mar. (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Reviews: Giving up the Ghost [Winn, Steven. "Hispanics blend into strange melting pot," San Francisco Chronicle Datebook (1989 Mar. 19): 25 - 28] 1989 Mar. 19 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Reviews: Giving up the Ghost ["Living in the shadows: a feminist speaks out," Santa Barbara News Press (1987 Oct. 2)] 1987 Oct. 2 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Reviews: Heroes and Saints [Acosta, Belinda. "Moraga taps into Chicana lifeline," Austin American-Statesman (1992 Oct. 24)] 1992 Oct. 24 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Reviews: Heroes and Saints [Fox, Michael. "Exposing the effects of pesticides," Sunday Independent (1992 Apr. 12)] 1992 Apr. 12 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Reviews: Heroes and Saints [Green, Judith. "Women's Work," San Jose Mercury News (1992 Apr. 10)] 1992 Apr. 10 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Reviews: Heroes and Saints [Harvey, Dennis. "High road, low road," San Francisco Weekly (1992 Apr. 8)] 1992 Apr. 8 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Reviews: Heroes and Saints [Haugen, Peter. "Rewriting their roles," The Sacramento Bee (1992 Apr. 5)] 1992 Apr. 5 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Reviews: Heroes and Saints [Hernandez, Monica. "Woman in hiding," Bay Area Reporter (1992 Apr. 9)] 1992 Apr. 9 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Reviews: Heroes and Saints [Hershenson, Karen. "Hero has head--that's all--for farm fight," Contra Costa Times (1992 Apr. 3)] 1992 Apr. 3 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Reviews: Heroes and Saints [Huerta, Jorge. "Cherríe Moraga's 'Heroes': Chicano Theatre for the 90s"] n.d. (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Reviews: Heroes and Saints [Jamison, Laura. "Fighter on the fringe." San Francisco Weekly.--Vol. 11, no. 5 (1992 Apr.)] 1992 Apr. (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Reviews: Heroes and Saints [Mackey, Heather. "Down on the farm." The Bay Guardian (1992 Apr. 8)] 1992 Apr.8 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Reviews: Heroes and Saints [Morales, Ed. "Shadowing Valdez." American Theatre.--Vol. 9, no. 7 (1992 Nov.)] 1992 Nov. (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Reviews: Heroes and Saints [Motola, Stuart. "Heroes and Saints!" Mission Life (1992 Mar.): 17] 1992 Mar. (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Reviews: Heroes and Saints [Reineccius, Richard. "Live in the Mission." New Mission Times (1992 Apr.): 16] 1992 Apr. (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Reviews: Heroes and Saints [Rosenberg, Scott. "Injustices stay all in the family." San Francisco Examiner (1992 Apr. 17)] 1992 Apr. 17 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Reviews: Heroes and Saints [Silva, Elda. "Play targets poisoning of land, lives." San Antonio Light (1992 Oct. 21)] 1992 Oct. 21 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Reviews: Heroes and Saints [Silva, Elda. "Heroes and Saints examines poisoning in our lives." San Antonio Light (1992 Oct. 22)] 1992 Oct. 22 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Reviews: Heroes and Saints [Turoff, Randy. "Playwright Cherríe Moraga presented by Brava!" San Francisco Bay Times (1992 Apr. 23): 38 - 39] 1992 Apr. 23 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Reviews: Heroes and Saints [Winn, Steven. "Courting Conflict in Lawyer Drama." San Francisco Chronicle (1993 Jan. 30) ] 1992 Jan. 30 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Reviews: Heroes and Saints [Winn, Steven. "Protest Theater Alive in the Mission." San Francisco Chronicle (1993 Apr. 21): E1 - E3 ] 1992 Apr. 21 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Reviews: Heroes and Saints ["Berkeley Rep tops critics awards." San Francisco Examiner (1993 Apr. 2): B3] 1992 Apr. 20 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Reviews: Heroes and Saints ["Brava! Para Mujeres..." Horizontes (1992 Mar. 20)] 1992 Mar. 20 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Reviews: Heroes and Saints ["Guadalupe Cultural Arts Center..." La Prensa de San Antonio (1992 Oct. 16)] 1992 Oct. 16 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Reviews: Heroes and Saints ["Heroes and Saints" The Monthly (1992 Apr.)] 1992 Apr. (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Reviews: The Last Generation [Clausen, Jan. "The Axis of Herstory." The Nation (1994 May 9): 634 - 637] 1994 May 9 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Reviews: The Last Generation [De la Peña, Terri. "Prism of Poetry, Lens on prose," Lambda Book Report] n.d. (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Reviews: The Last Generation [Johnson, Richard. "Naked honesty deplores loss of Mexican culture." Denver Post (1994 Jan. 2) 1994 Jan. 2 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Reviews: The Last Generation [Martinez, Elizabeth. Untitled. Z Magazine (1994 Feb.): 57 - 59] 1994 Feb. (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Reviews: The Last Generation [Stavans, Ilan. "Art and Anger." In these times (1994 July 25): 32 - 34] 1994 July 25 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Reviews: The Last Generation [Thompson, Becky. Untitled.] 1994 Feb. (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Reviews: The Last Generation [Thompson, Becky. Book review. Notas.--Vol. 2, no. 2 (1994 Feb.): 5 - 7] 1994 Feb. (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Reviews: The Last Generation [Torres, Lourdes. "Chicana writers explore the land in the middle." Sojourner (1994 Aug.)] 1994 Aug. (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Reviews: The Last Generation [Wheatwind, Marie-Elise. "All in the Familia." Women's Review of Books.--Vol. 11, no. 4 (1994 Jan.)] 1994 Jan. (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Reviews: Loving in the war years [Rodriguez, Juan. "Chicano Literature." Tonantzin (1984 Feb. - Mar.): 13] 1984 Feb. -Mar. (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Reviews: Loving in the war years [Shafarzek, Susan. "LJ's small press roundup: best titles of 1984" Library Journal (1984 Nov. 15): 2113 - 2118] 1984 Nov. 15 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Reviews: Loving in the war years [Stone, Arlene. "Blood Roots." Contact II] n.d. (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Reviews: Shadow of a Man [Ayres, Jane. "Latina Power." Peninsula Times Tribune (1990 Nov. 12)] 1990 Nov. 12 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Reviews: Shadow of a Man [Barber, Matthew. "María Irene Fornes." San Francisco Independent.--Vol. 35, no. 82 (1990 Nov. 15): 1 - 2] 1990 Nov. 15 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Reviews: Shadow of a Man [Barnes, Noreen C. "An ideal combination'," San Francisco Bay Area Reporter (1990 Nov. 8): 1, 40] 1990 Nov. 8 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Reviews: Shadow of a Man [Barnes, Noreen C. "A splendid balance'," San Francisco Bay Area Reporter, 1990 Nov. 15, p. 35] 1990 Nov. 15 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Reviews: Shadow of a Man [Berson, Misha. "'Shadow of a Man' Brings Light.. .," Datebook, Nov. 4, 1990, p. 37] 1990 Nov. 4 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Reviews: Shadow of a Man [Cariaga, Catalina. "The Poetics of Chisme," Poetry Flash. -- No. 195 (1989 June)] 1989 June (Box 2, Folder 63)
    .
  - Reviews: Shadow of a Man [Coates, Mari. "Brava! For Women in the Arts," San Francisco Sentinel, Nov. 8, 1990, p. 19.] 1990 Nov. 8 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Reviews: Shadow of a Man [Coates, Mari. "Interview with María Irene Fornes," San Francisco Sentinel, Nov. 15, 1990, p. 18.] 1990 Nov. 15 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Reviews: Shadow of a Man [Fishman, Ted. C. "The Latino Chicago Theater Company," Chicago's News & Arts Weekly, June 11-17, 1992.] 1992 June 11-17 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Reviews: Shadow of a Man [Haugen, Peter. "'Shadow' is emotion.. .," The Sacramento Bee Final, Nov. 12, 1990, p. e3.] 1990 Nov. 12 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Reviews: Shadow of a Man [Haugen, Peter. "Bario Drama in the Kitchen-sink Tradition," Theater Review, Nov. 13, 1990.] 1990 Nov. 13 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Reviews: Shadow of a Man [Haugen, Peter. "'Shadow' is a kitchen-sink drama that offers free-flowing emotions," [San Mateo, CA] Times, Nov. 14, 1990.] 1990 Nov. 14 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Reviews: Shadow of a Man [Haugen, Peter. "Ambitious 'Shadow of a Man' is an emotion-charged drama," Alameda Times Star, Nov. 15, 1990.] 1990 Nov. 15 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Reviews: Shadow of a Man [Jarrett, Charles. "Powerful Play Looks at Hispanic Society."] n.d. (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Reviews: Shadow of a Man [Lee, Walter. "Shadow of a man premieres at Eureka," San Francisco Arts Monthly.--Vol. 1, no. 8 (1990 Nov.)] 1990 Nov. (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Reviews: Shadow of a Man [Lewis, Andrea. "The Next Stage, " Mother Jones, Jan/Feb. 1991, p. 15.] 1991 Jan/Feb. (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Reviews: Shadow of a Man [Lovato, Robert. " Yo Existo," The City, Vol. 1, no. 6 (Nov. 1990), pp. 23-24.] 1990 Nov. (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Reviews: Shadow of a Man [MacMinn, Aleene. "Stage," Los Angeles Times., n.d.] n.d. (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Reviews: Shadow of a Man [Noyes, Katia. "The Dream Images of Cherríe Moraga," San Francisco Sentinel, Nov. 8, 1990.] 1990 Nov. 8 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Reviews: Shadow of a Man [Noyes, Katia. "Disintegration of Machismo," San Francisco Sentinel, n.d.] n.d. (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Reviews: Shadow of a Man [Scott, Nancy. "ACT's Theater within," San Francisco Examiner, Apr. 19, 1989, p. c3.] 1989 Apr. 19 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Reviews: Shadow of a Man [Shaw, Stephanie. "Shadow of a Man," Reader, Vol. 21, no. 36 (1992 June 12).] 1992 June 12 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Reviews: Shadow of a Man [Weiss, Hedy. "Remarkable acting makes for riveting 'Shadow of a Man,'" Chicago Sun-Times, Jun. 9, 1992.] 1992 June 9 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Reviews: Shadow of a Man [Winn, Steven. "Macho drives drama.. .," [San Francisco] Chronicle, Nov. 14, 1990.] 1990 Nov. 14 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Reviews: Shadow of a Man [Winn, Steven. "Hispanics Blend into Stage Melting Pot, " SF Chronicle Datebook, Mar. 19, 1989, pp. 25-26.] 1989 Mar. 19 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Reviews: Shadow of a Man [Wright, Sheila. "'Shadow of a man' play gives honest view," [Antioch, CA] Daily Ledger-Post Dispatch, Nov. 15, 1990] 1990 Nov. 15 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Reviews: Shadow of a Man ["Calendar," San Francisco Focus, pp. 170 & 180.] n.d. (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Reviews: Shadow of a Man ["Chicago Family is the Center of San Francisco Production," Press Release for Allen's DCB, Nov. 10, 1990.] 1990 Nov. 10 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Reviews: Shadow of a Man ["Drama details 'machismo'," Nov. 1, 1990.] 1990 Nov. 1 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Reviews: Shadow of a Man ["La Verdadera excelencia de 'Sombra de un Hombre.'"] n.d. (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Reviews: Shadow of a Man ["Stages," American Theatre (1990) 1990 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Reviews: Shadow of a Man ["Sombra de un Hombre: Moraga y Fornes combina sus talentos," El Tecolote, Nov. 1990, pp. 4-5.] 1990 Nov. (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Reviews: This Bridge Called my Back [Porter, Veneita. "The 'Bridge' at the Blackstone: Third World Women's Reading," Gay Community News, Oct. 18, 1980, p. 11] 1980 Oct. 18 (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Reviews: This Bridge Called My Back [Zima, Elizabeth. "Conference on Racism speaker asks awareness, The Daily Iowan, May 3, 1982.] 1982 May 3 (Box 2, Folder 91)
- Series XIV. Photographs, Posters, and Awards
  - Cadden, Wendy. "Amazon II" [no. 7 of 10] 1980 (Box MC)
    1 original artwork: color photo duplication [?]
  - Castillo, Ana. "In my country" [note: signed by author "San Francisco, 1986"] 1986 (Box MC)
    1 original artwork: watercolor and type on paper
  - "Ana Castillo, Cherríe Moraga, Visiting Professors of Creative Writing, 'Evolution of the Chicana Writer: a Personal Literary History" n.d. [Mar. 19 -21] (Box MC)
    1 poster
  - "Cherríe Moraga and Ana Castillo: Latina Identity: Poetics and Politics, a reading" n.d. [Apr. 17] (Box MC)
  - Hernandez, Ester. "Brava! For Women in the Arts presents The World Premiere of Heroes and Saints by Cherríe Moraga, directed by Albert Takazauckas" [no. 10 of 57] [note: signed by the artist and Cherríe Moraga] 1992 (Box MC)
    1 original artwork: print on paper
  - "Heroes and Saints: Dartmouth Department of Drama Presents Heroes and Saints..." n.d. [Feb. 20 -25] (Box MC)
  - "Oakes Lecture Series... present an evening with Cherríe Moraga and Ana Castillo, Chicana Writers and Poets" 1987 Dec. 7 (Box MC)
  - "Old World, New World: Three Hispanic Photographers, Seattle Art Museum" 1991 Aug. 8 -Nov. 3 (Box MC)
  - "Shadow of a Man, written by Cherríe Moraga, directed by María Irene Fornes, Eureka Theatre Company, San Francisco" 1990 Nov. 10 -Dec. 9 (Box MC)
  - "Watsonville: Some Place Not Here, by Cherríe Moraga, The Brava Theater Center, San Francisco, directed by Amy Mueller" [note: signed and dated by Cherríe Moraga] 1996 May 25 -June 30 (Box MC)
  - "Women's Studies presents: Cherríe Moraga 'Giving Up the Ghost: a Poetry Performance" [2 copies] n.d. [Dec. 1] (Box MC)
  - Unidentified artist. Untitled [image of three women with birds] n.d. (Box MC)
    1 original artwork: watercolor and ink on paper
  - Adams, Barbara. Untitled. 1982 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    1 photograph: b & w; 12 x 17 cm.
  - "Alurista" 1987 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    1 photograph: col.; 9 x 13 cm.
  - "Benefit NCLR" 1992 -1993 [?] (Box 1, Folder 3)
    1 photograph: b & w; 13 x 13 cm.
  - Cohen, Shari. Giving up the Ghost 1989 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Dong, Lily. Untitled 1989 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    1 photograph: b & w; 18 x 12 cm.
  - Dong, Lily. Untitled 1989 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    2 photographs: b & w; 25 x 20 cm.
  - "Drama Divas 92" 1992 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - "Germany" 1987 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Giving Up the Ghost, Actons's Direction ["Belinda, Me, Anita, Ana y Linda"] n.d. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - [Giving Up the Ghost]. Ghost opening Seattle, Laura Esporza, Dir. n.d. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - [Giving Up the Ghost]. Ghost Staged Play, Mission Cultural Center 1987 [?] (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - "Gloria Anzaldúa, Jo Carrillo & C.M." 1979 -1980 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    1 photograph: b & w; 8 x 12 cm.
  - "Gloria Anzaldúa with Sally Gearhart, S.F." 1979 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - "Guadalupe García" n.d. (Box 1, Folder 14)
    1 photograph: col.; 16 x 11 cm.
  - [Heroes & Saints] n.d. (Box 1, Folder 15)
    7 photographs: col.; 11 x 16 cm.
  - [Heroes & Saints] n.d. (Box 1, Folder 16)
    8 photographs: col.; 9 x 13 cm.
  - H[eroes] & S[aints] Environmental Justice Group n.d. (Box 1, Folder 17)
    1 photograph: col.; 11 x 16 cm.
  - Image Magazine. Untitled n.d. (Box 1, Folder 18)
    2 photographs: col.; 8 x 10 cm.
  - "Iowa" 1992 Feb. 24 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - "Juan Felipe Hevrera, Fresno" 1987 [?] (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Koolish, Lynda. Untitled n.d. (Box 1, Folder 21)
    2 photographs (facs.): b & w; 25 x 20 cm. 1 ALS
  - "Llegó Conference" 1992 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    2 photographs: col.; 11 x 16 cm.
  - "Mexico City with Sandro Cisnevos, in front of Malinche's home" 1985 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    1 photograph: col.; 13 x 9 cm.
  - "Mexico Trip" [includes Poricutin Volcano (Michoacón), ILGA Conference, artist Ian Castro] 1992 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    8 photographs: col.; 11 x 15 cm.
  - "La Missión" n.d. (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - "Navajo Nation" n.d. (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - "N[ew] M[exico]" n.d. (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - "New Mexico," Anaya's N.M. 1988 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    4 photographs: col.; 13 x 9 cm.
  - [Oakland, CA] 1987 -1988 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    8 photographs: b & w; 13 x 9 cm.
  - "Oaxaca" 1989 Dec. (Box 1, Folder 30)
    2 photographs: col.; 9 x 13 cm.
  - Pelaez, Annette. Kitchen Table Press Office, NYC 1983 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    1 photograph: b & w; 18 x 13 cm.
  - Pelaez, Annette. Kitchen Table Press with Ana Oliveiras & Rosie Aluzrez [?] 1983 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    1 photograph: b & w; 13 x 18 cm.
  - Pelaez, Annette. NYWAR Conference 1985 May (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Pelaez, Annette. Untitled 1983 [?] (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - "Piri Thomas, Rodrigo Reyes, Norma Alarcón, Juan Felipe, Fresno" 1987 [?] (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - "Reading with A. Castillo, Galería de la Raza, S.F." n.d. (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - "Red Hot, Brown Funk / Brown Sounds from the Underground. UCB Creative Writing Class Reading. 12/6/90 Cherríe Moraga" 1990 Dec. 6 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    1 photograph: col.; 12 x 9 cm.
  - "Ruth Foreman" 1993 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - "San Antonio, Tejas" 1984 July (Box 1, Folder 39)
    1 photograph: b & w; 13 x 9 cm.
  - "Santa Cruz reading" 1986 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    2 photographs (1 facs.): b & w; 12 x 9 cm.
  - Schuerholz, Dana. Untitled. n.d. (Box 1, Folder 41)
    1 photograph: b & w; 13 x 19 cm.
  - "S.F. Gay march" 1977 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    1 photograph: b & w; 17 x 12 cm.
  - [Shadow of a Man] n.d. (Box 1, Folder 43)
    11 photographs: col.; 11 x 16 cm.
  - "Shadow of a Man Promo, with María Irene Fornes" 1990 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    2 photographs: b & w; 16 x 24 cm.
  - "South Coast Repertory" n.d. (Box 1, Folder 45)
    2 photographs: b & w; 19 x 24 cm.
  - "Univeristy of California, Berkeley, Theater class" n.d. (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Wiesenger, Jean. Untitled 1993 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    3 photographs: b & w; 16 x 11 cm.
  - Wiesenger, Jean. Untitled 1993 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Wilson, Susan. Cherríe Moraga 1981 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    1 photograph: b & w; 22 x 19 cm.
  - [Women Poets at Barnard] 1993 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Unidentified photographs n.d. (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Wiesenger, Jean. Untitled 1993 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    1 photograph: b & w; 21 x 14 cm.
  - [Shadow of a Man] [Raddatz, K, photographer?] n.d. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    3 contact sheets: b & w
  - The Out/Look Foundation, Out Write 1991 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    1 wood & metal plaque: 18 x 23 cm.
  - Garcia, Guadalupe. Para Cherríe- Poetiza encarna mujer n.d. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    1 original artwork: photograph, applique, feathers; 37 x 29 cm.
- Series XV. Oversize
  - The New woman's survival catalog. [Editors: Kirsten Grimstad and Susan Rennie]. New York, Coward, McCann & Geoghegan [1973]. 223 p. illus. 37 cm. 1973 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Moraga, Cherríe. "Wanting 'It': The Power of Latinas," The Advocate.--Issue 426 (1985 Aug. 6): 40 - 41 1985 Aug. 6 (Box 1, Folder 2)